http://www.metalcenternews.com/contact/privacy-statement

Special Sections
Search by Category:
Special Sections
Search By Category:
Privacy Statement
Metal Center News is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Metal Center News Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Metal Center News website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Metal Center News collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Metal Center News also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Metal Center News. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Metal Center News for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Metal Center News Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Metal Center News public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Metal Center News does not read any of your private online communications.
Metal Center News encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Metal Center News so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Metal Center News is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Metal Center News and Metal Center News family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Metal Center News collects and uses your personal information to operate the Metal Center News Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Metal Center News also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Metal Center News and its affiliates. Metal Center News may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Metal Center News does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Metal Center News may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Metal Center News may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Metal Center News, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Metal Center News does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Metal Center News keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Metal Center News, in order to determine what Metal Center News services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Metal Center News to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Metal Center News Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Metal Center News or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Metal Center News; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Metal Center News, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Metal Center News Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Metal Center News pages, or register with Metal Center News site or services, a cookie helps Metal Center News to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Metal Center News Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Metal Center News features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Metal Center News services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Metal Center News secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Metal Center News secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Metal Center News will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Metal Center News encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Metal Center News is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Metal Center News welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Metal Center News has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Metal Center News at info@metalcenternews.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Home
Editorial
Current Issue
Current News
Search Back Issues
Special Sections
Search by Category:
Copyright © 2020 Metal Center News All Rights Reserved.
Website Design and Development By JET Advertising
